import type { ContentItem } from "./types"

export const scienceContent: ContentItem[] = [
  {
    type: "exercise",
    question: "science_exercise_planet_red_question",
    correctAnswer: "science_exercise_planet_red_correctAnswer",
  },
  {
    type: "exercise",
    question: "science_exercise_human_body_blood_question",
    correctAnswer: "science_exercise_human_body_blood_correctAnswer",
  },
  {
    type: "exercise",
    question: "science_exercise_element_h2o_question",
    correctAnswer: "science_exercise_element_h2o_correctAnswer",
  },
  {
    type: "exercise",
    question: "science_exercise_animal_largest_marine_question",
    correctAnswer: "science_exercise_animal_largest_marine_correctAnswer",
  },
  {
    type: "exercise",
    question: "science_exercise_phenomenon_light_rain_question",
    correctAnswer: "science_exercise_phenomenon_light_rain_correctAnswer",
  },
  {
    type: "exercise",
    question: "science_exercise_sense_sight_question",
    correctAnswer: "science_exercise_sense_sight_correctAnswer",
  },
  {
    type: "exercise",
    question: "science_exercise_energy_solar_question",
    correctAnswer: "science_exercise_energy_solar_correctAnswer",
  },
  {
    type: "exercise",
    question: "science_exercise_gas_breathe_question",
    correctAnswer: "science_exercise_gas_breathe_correctAnswer",
  },
  {
    type: "exercise",
    question: "science_exercise_cycle_water_question",
    correctAnswer: "science_exercise_cycle_water_correctAnswer",
  },
  {
    type: "exercise",
    question: "science_exercise_force_pulls_down_question",
    correctAnswer: "science_exercise_force_pulls_down_correctAnswer",
  },
  {
    type: "exercise",
    question: "science_exercise_planet_largest_question",
    correctAnswer: "science_exercise_planet_largest_correctAnswer",
  },
  {
    type: "exercise",
    question: "science_exercise_body_system_breathing_question",
    correctAnswer: "science_exercise_body_system_breathing_correctAnswer",
  },
  {
    type: "exercise",
    question: "science_exercise_chemical_element_gold_question",
    correctAnswer: "science_exercise_chemical_element_gold_correctAnswer",
  },
  {
    type: "exercise",
    question: "science_exercise_animal_fastest_land_question",
    correctAnswer: "science_exercise_animal_fastest_land_correctAnswer",
  },
  {
    type: "exercise",
    question: "science_exercise_state_matter_ice_question",
    correctAnswer: "science_exercise_state_matter_ice_correctAnswer",
  },
  {
    type: "exercise",
    question: "science_exercise_organ_filters_blood_question",
    correctAnswer: "science_exercise_organ_filters_blood_correctAnswer",
  },
  {
    type: "exercise",
    question: "science_exercise_natural_disaster_tornado_question",
    correctAnswer: "science_exercise_natural_disaster_tornado_correctAnswer",
  },
  {
    type: "exercise",
    question: "science_exercise_unit_force_question",
    correctAnswer: "science_exercise_unit_force_correctAnswer",
  },
  {
    type: "exercise",
    question: "science_exercise_process_plants_food_question",
    correctAnswer: "science_exercise_process_plants_food_correctAnswer",
  },
  {
    type: "exercise",
    question: "science_exercise_body_part_brain_question",
    correctAnswer: "science_exercise_body_part_brain_correctAnswer",
  },
]
